Finding Aid for the SOUL Publications, Inc. records PASC-M.0342
UCLA Library Special Collections
SOUL Publications, Inc. records
1955-2002
UCLA Library Special Collections
SOUL Publications, Inc., 1966-1982
PASC-M.0342
37.2 linear feet (70 document boxes, 1 oversize box, and 6 shoe boxes)
3 linear feet (3 unprocessed record cartons)
SOUL Magazine was the principal publication of SOUL Publications, Inc., a Los Angeles-based enterprise founded by Regina and Ken Jones in 1966. Initially established to engender greater visibility for Black artists in the music industry, SOUL ultimately provided a space for critical engagement with Black artistic expression as well as social issues. The collection includes newspaper and magazine issues, research and clipping files on artists and public figures, audio cassettes of interviews and performances, photographs, and administrative files.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
CONTAINS AUDIO MATERIALS: This collection contains both processed and unprocessed audio materials. Audio materials are not currently available for access, unless otherwise noted in a Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note at the series and file levels. All requests to access processed digital materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Regina Jones, 2010.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9966514643606533
Biography
SOUL Publications was established in 1966 in Los Angeles by Regina and Ken Jones. The impetus for SOUL was the Watts Riots, which inspired local newsman Ken Jones to develop a vehicle for documenting and expressing the African American perspective in a self-representative way. Equipped with his vision and the industrious drive of his wife, Regina Jones, the company initially focused on providing promotion and recognition for Black musicians, who received scant publicity at that time. Its publications grew to include other aspects of Black cultural production, including film, television, literature, and the visual arts.
SOUL, a newspaper later renamed SOUL Magazine, was published from 1966-1982. The Joneses utilized the innovative quarter-fold format so that the newspaper could be conveniently placed on the counter next to cash registers and sold in shops in the African American community. SOUL was first sold only in Los Angeles, in conjunction with local R&B radio station KGFJ. As a result of marketing arrangements with other R&B radio affiliates nationwide, its circulation expanded, and it attained a circulation of 125,000 in approximately 30 major markets. The term "soul radio" is a testament to the legacy of the publication.
By providing visibility for African American artists, SOUL filled a palpable need, and as a result, the publication was granted access to many up-and-coming entertainers who were grateful to receive the exposure offered by the publication. Many of these artists - James Brown, Aretha Franklin, Stevie Wonder, Marvin Gaye, the Temptations, Smokey Robinson, Diana Ross and the Supremes, and the Jacksons - are now considered legends.
The sister publication of the newspaper was SOUL Illustrated, a glossy magazine ran from 1968-1972. SOUL Illustrated began with an entertainment focus similar to the newspaper but gradually came to tackle social, political, and racial issues to a greater degree. The publication reveals the evolving social consciousness of its time, serving as a forum for critical dialogue on such topics as Black liberation, images of African Americans in the media, and the Vietnam War.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of issues of SOUL/SOUL Magazine and SOUL Illustrated, research files, audio cassettes of interviews and performances, photographs, and administrative files. Significant individuals represented in issues, research files, and photographs include: James Brown, Aretha Franklin, Muhammad Ali, Berry Gordy, Jr., Stevie Wonder, Sidney Poitier, Smokey Robinson, the Temptations, Marvin Gaye, the Jackson Five, the Fifth Dimension, Gladys Knight and the Pips, Diana Ross, the Supremes, Quincy Jones, Isaac Hayes, and Jesse Jackson.
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged in the following series:
SOUL issues (Boxes 1-16 and 77).
Research files (Boxes 17-56).
Audio cassettes (Boxes 57-62).
Photographs (Boxes 63-76).
Administrative files (Box 77).
Online Items Available
Portions of this collection have been digitized and are available online: SOUL Publications, Inc. records (7 items).
SOUL Illustrated; SOUL/SOUL Magazine
- 1. SOUL Issues, 1966-1982
  Scope and Contents note
  SOUL publications, including individual issues of SOUL Illustrated, SOUL Newspaper, and SOUL Magazine; bound issues; and microfilm.
  - Soul Illustrated, Volume 1, Number 1, 1968 Summer (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Soul Illustrated, Volume 1, Number 2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Soul Illustrated, Volume 1, Number 3, 1968 Winter (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Soul Illustrated, Volume 1, Number 4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Soul Illustrated, Volume 1, Number 5, 1969 June (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Soul Illustrated, Volume 1, Number 6, 1969 August (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Soul Illustrated, Volume 2, Number 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Soul Illustrated, Volume 2, Number 2 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Soul Illustrated, Volume 2, Number 3, 1970 February (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Soul Illustrated, Volume 2, Number 4, 1970 July (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Soul Illustrated, Volume 2, Number 5 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Soul Illustrated, Volume 2, Number 6 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Soul Illustrated, Volume 3, Number 1, 1971 April (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Soul Illustrated, Volume 3, Number 2, 1971 Fall (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Soul Illustrated, Volume 3, Number 3 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Soul Illustrated, Volume 3, Number 4 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Soul Illustrated, Volume 3, Number 5, 1972 Summer (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Soul Illustrated, Volumes 1-2, Bound Issues, 1968 Summer-1970 December (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Soul (KGFJ Soul), Volume 1, Number 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    "White artists selling Negro 'soul'"
  - Soul (KGFJ Soul), Volume 1, Number 2, 1966 April 21 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    "Little Richard declares war"
  - Soul (KGFJ Soul), Volume 1, Number 3 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Soul (KGFJ Soul), Volume 1, Number 4 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Soul (KGFJ Soul), Volume 1, Number 5, 1966 May 12 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Soul (KGFJ Soul), Volume 1, Number 6, 1966 May 19 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Soul (KGFJ Soul), Volume 1, Number 7 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Soul (KGFJ Soul), Volume 1, Number 8 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Soul (KGFJ Soul), Volume 1, Number 9, 1966 June 9 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Soul (KGFJ Soul), Volume 1, Number 10, 1966 June 16 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Soul (KGFJ Soul), Volume 1, Number 11 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Soul (KGFJ Soul), Volume 1, Number 12 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Soul (KGFJ Soul), Volume 1, Number 13, 1966 July 7 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Soul (KGFJ Soul), Volume 1, Number 14, 1966 July 14 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Soul (KGFJ Soul), Volume 1, Number 15 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Soul (KGFJ Soul), Volume 1, Number 18 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Soul (KGFJ Soul), Volume 1, Number 22, 1966 October 13 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Soul (KGFJ Soul), Volume 1, Number 25, 1966 November 24 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Soul (KGFJ Soul), Volume 1, Number 30 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 1, Number 30 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 1, Number 31, 1967 March 2 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition - Boss Soul), Volume 1, Number 3, 1967 March 16 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition - Boss Soul), Volume 1, Number 5 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition - Boss Soul), Volume 1, Number 6 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition - KGFJ Soul), Volume 2, Number 6, 1967 June 22 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Soul (WOL Edition), Volume 1, Number 3, 1967 July 6 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Soul (KCOH Edition), Volume 1, Number 2 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Soul (WOL Edition), Volume 1, Number 6 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Soul (WDAS Edition), Volume 1, Number 7, 1967 September 4 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Soul (WABQ Edition), Volume 1, Number 6, 1967 September 18 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Soul (KCOH Edition), Volume 1, Number 7 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Soul (WAOK Edition), Volume 1, Number 7 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Soul (WEBB Edition), Volume 1, Number 11, 1967 October 30 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Soul (WJLB Edition - Boss Soul), Volume 1, Number 13, 1967 November 27 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Soul (WJLD Edition), Volume 1, Number 10 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition - Boss Soul), Volume 1, Number 23 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Soul (WOL Edition), Volume 1, Number 16, 1968 January 15 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Soul (WUFO Edition), Volume 1, Number 15, 1968 January 29 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Soul (WUFO Edition), Volume 2, Number 22 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Soul (WEBB Edition), Volume 2, Number 23 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 2, Number 24, 1968 March 11 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Soul (WYLD Edition), Volume 2, Number 25, 1968 March 25 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition - Boss Soul), Volume 2, Number 26 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Soul (WJLB Edition - Boss Soul), Volume 2, Number 27 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Soul (WLOU Edition), Volume 3, Number 2, 1968 May 20 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 3, Number 3, 1968 June 3 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Soul (WWRL Edition), Volume 3, Number 4 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Soul, Volume 3, Number 5 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Soul, Volume 3, Number 6, 1968 July 15 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 3, Number 7, 1968 July 29 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    "Soul exclusive: Lena Horne"
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 3, Number 8 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Soul (DJ Trade Edition), Volume 3, Number 9, 1968 August 26 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Soul (WWRL Edition), Volume 3, Number 10, 1968 September 9 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Soul, Volume 3, Number 13 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 3, Number 14 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 3, Number 15, 1968 November 4 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 3, Number 16, 1968 November 18 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Soul (WWRL Edition), Volume 3, Number 17 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Soul (WWRL Edition), Volume 3, Number 18 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Soul, Volume 3, Number 19, 1968 December 30 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    "Sidney Poitier breaks the image"
  - Soul, Volume 3, Number 21, 1969 January 20 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 3, Number 23 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 3, Number 24, 1969 March 3 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 3, Number 25, 1969 March 17 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Soul, Volume 3, Number 26 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 3, Number 27 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 4, Number 1, 1969 May 19 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    3rd anniversary issue
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 4, Number 2, 1969 June 2 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Soul, Volume 4, Number 3 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 4, Number 4, 1969 June 30 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 4, Number 5, 1969 July 14 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Soul (WWRL Edition), Volume 4, Number 6 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    "J.B. changes image" [James Brown]
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 4, Number 8, 1969 August 25 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 4, Number 9, 1969 September 8 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 4, Number 10 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Soul, Volume 4, Number 11, 1969 October 6 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    "Aretha retires"
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 4, Number 12, 1969 October 20 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 4, Number 13 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 4, Number 14, 1969 November 17 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 4, Number 16, 1969 December 15 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    "Angela Davis: Black, beautiful, and red"
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 4, Number 17 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 4, Number 18, 1970 January 12 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 4, Number 19, 1970 February 9 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 4, Number 20 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 4, Number 21 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 4, Number 22, 1970 March 23 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 4, Number 23, 1970 April 6 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 4, Number 24 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    "Tammi Terrell dead, 1946-1970"
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 4, Number 25, 1970 May 4 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 4, Number 26, 1970 May 18 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 5, Number 1 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    "The Jackson 5: world's most soulful family"
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 5, Number 2, 1970 June 15 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    Jackie Jackson
  - Soul, Volume 5, Number 3 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    Tito Jackson
  - Soul (WWRL Edition), Volume 5, Number 3 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    Jermaine Jackson
  - Soul (WWRL Edition), Volume 5, Number 4, 1970 July 27 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    Marlon Jackson
  - Soul, Volume 5, Number 5 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    Michael Jackson
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 5, Number 7 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Soul, Volume 5, Number 8, 1970 September 7 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    "The Temptations: how it all began"
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 5, Number 9, 1970 September 21 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    Otis Williams of the Temptations
  - Soul, Volume 5, Number 10 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    Melvin Franklin of the Temptations
  - Soul (Boss KDIA Edition), Volume 5, Number 11, 1970 October 19 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    Paul Williams of the Temptations
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 5, Number 12 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    "What killed Jimi?" / Dennis Edwards of the Temptations
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 5, Number 13 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Eddie Kendricks of the Temptations
  - Soul (WWRL Edition), Volume 5, Number 14, 1970 November 30 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 5, Number 15, 1970 December 14 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 5, Number 16 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Soul (Boss KDIA Edition), Volume 5, Number 17, 1971 January 11 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 5, Number 18, 1971 January 25 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 5, Number 19 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 5, Number 21 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 5, Number 22, 1971 March 22 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Soul (WWRL Edition), Volume 5, Number 23, 1971 April 5 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Soul (KDIA, WVON, WWRL Edition), Volume 6, Number 1 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    5th anniversary issue
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 6, Number 2, 1971 May 24 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Soul, Volume 6, Number 3, 1971 June 7 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Soul (WWRL Edition), Volume 6, Number 4 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 6, Number 5, 1971 July 5 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 6, Number 6, 1971 July 19 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Soul (Boss KDIA Edition), Volume 6, Number 7 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 6, Number 8 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 6, Number 9, 1971 August 30 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 6, Number 10, 1971 September 13 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 6, Number 11 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Soul (Boss KDIA Edition), Volume 6, Number 12 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Soul (Boss KDIA Edition), Volume 6, Number 13, 1971 October 25 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Soul (Boss KDIA Edition), Volume 6, Number 14, 1971 November 8 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 6, Number 15 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Soul (Boss KDIA Edition), Volume 6, Number 16 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 6, Number 17, 1971 December 20 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Soul, Volume 6, Number 18, 1972 January 4 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Soul, Volume 6, Number 19 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Soul, Volume 6, Number 19 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 6, Number 21, 1972 February 14 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    "Will Michael Jackson go solo in '72?"
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 6, Number 22, 1972 February 28 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Soul, Volume 6, Number 23 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Soul (WWRL Edition), Volume 6, Number 24, 1972 March 27 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Soul (WWRL Edition), Volume 6, Number 25, 1972 April 10 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Soul (KDIA, KGFJ, WVON, WWRL Edition), Volume 7, Number 1 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    6th anniversary issue
  - Soul (Boss KDIA Edition), Volume 7, Number 2, 1972 May 22 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Soul (WWRL Edition), Volume 7, Number 3, 1972 June 5 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 7, Number 4 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 7, Number 5, 1972 July 3 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 7, Number 6, 1972 July 17 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 7, Number 7 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 7, Number 8 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Soul, Volume 7, Number 9, 1972 August 28 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 7, Number 10, 1972 September 11 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Soul, Volume 7, Number 11 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Soul (WWRL Edition), Volume 7, Number 12 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    "Black Moses leads 100,000 to Wattstax"
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 7, Number 13, 1972 October 23 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Soul (WWRL Edition), Volume 7, Number 14, 1972 November 6 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 7, Number 15 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Soul (WWRL Edition), Volume 7, Number 16, 1972 December 4 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 7, Number 17, 1972 December 18 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    "A special report on Black films: who's making all the money?"
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 7, Number 18 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 7, Number 19, 1973 January 16 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 7, Number 20, 1973 January 29 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Soul (WWRL Edition), Volume 7, Number 21 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 7, Number 22 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Soul (WWRL Edition), Volume 7, Number 23, 1973 March 12 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 7, Number 24, 1973 March 26 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 7, Number 25 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Soul, Volume 7, Number 26 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    7th anniversary issue
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 8, Number 2, 1973 May 14 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 8, Number 3, 1973 May 28 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 8, Number 4 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 8, Number 5, 1973 June 25 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Soul (National Edition), Volume 8, Number 6, 1973 July 9 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 8, Number 7 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 8, Number 8 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 8, Number 9, 1973 August 20 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 8, Number 10, 1973 September 3 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 8, Number 11 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    "'Superfly's Ron O'Neal squares off at White filmmakers: White TV admen say: 'Talk Black'"
  - Soul (National Edition), Volume 8, Number 12, 1973 October 1 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 8, Number 13, 1973 October 15 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 8, Number 14 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 8, Number 15, 1973 November 12 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 8, Number 16, 1973 November 26 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Soul (National Edition), Volume 8, Number 17 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 8, Number 18 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 8, Number 19, 1974 January 7 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Soul (KGFJ), Volume 8, Number 20, 1974 January 21 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Soul (KGFJ), Volume 8, Number 21 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 8, Number 22 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 8, Number 24, 1974 March 18 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 8, Number 23, 1974 March 4 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 8, Number 25 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 8, Number 26 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Soul (KGFJ, WVON, KDIA Edition), Volume 9, Number 1, 1974 April 29 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    8th anniversary issue
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 9, Number 2, 1974 May 13 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 9, Number 3 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 9, Number 4, 1974 June 10 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 9, Number 5, 1974 June 24 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Soul (National Edition), Volume 9, Number 6 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 9, Number 7 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Soul (National Edition), Volume 9, Number 8, 1974 August 5 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 9, Number 9, 1974 August 19 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Soul (National Edition), Volume 9, Number 10 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 9, Number 11 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 9, Number 12, 1974 September 30 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 9, Number 13, 1974 October 14 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 9, Number 14 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 9, Number 15 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 9, Number 16, 1974 November 25 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 9, Number 17, 1974 December 9 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    "Salute to Quincy Jones"
  - Soul (National Edition), Volume 9, Number 18 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    "Hollywood romances: Black and White getting it on"
  - Soul (National Edition), Volume 9, Number 19, 1975 January 6 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    "Black & White love, part two"
  - Soul (National Edition), Volume 9, Number 20, 1975 January 20 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Soul (National Edition), Volume 9, Number 21 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 9, Number 22, 1975 February 17 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    "Readers react to inter-racial love"
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 9, Number 23, 1975 March 3 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 9, Number 24 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 9, Number 25, 1975 March 31 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Soul (National Edition), Volume 9, Number 26, 1975 April 14 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 10, Number 1 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 10, Number 2 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 10, Number 3, 1975 May 26 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    9th anniversary issue
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 10, Number 4, 1975 June 9 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Soul (National Edition), Volume 10, Number 5 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Soul (National Edition), Volume 10, Number 6, 1975 July 7 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 10, Number 7, 1975 July 21 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Soul, Volume 10, Number 9 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 10, Number 10 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 10, Number 11, 1975 September 15 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Soul, Volume 10, Number 12, 1975 September 29 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    "Randy & Janet: stardom too soon?" [Randy and Janet Jackson]
  - Soul, Volume 10, Number 13 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 10, Number 14, 1975 October 27 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 10, Number 15, 1975 November 10 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Soul, Volume 10, Number 16 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Soul, Volume 10, Number 17 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Soul (WLIB Edition), Volume 10, Number 18, 1975 December 22 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 10, Number 19, 1976 January 5 (Box 10, Folder 5)